A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, SG 1, Series 20 FA292
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowship Files, 1920-1993; 2; 242 Box(es)
  - Round, Jeffrey Ian - 1968 - England - Economics and Regional Science, 1967-1979 (Box 183, Folder 1477)
  - Rowan, Harold - 1933 - England - Civil Engineerin, 1933-1977 (Box 183, Folder 1478)
  - Rowe, Henry Peter - 1955 - Germany - Civil Engineering, 1955-1988 (Box 183, Folder 1479)
  - Rowe, Richard - 1964 - England - Fluid Mechanics, 1963-1975 (Box 183, Folder 1480)
  - Rowland, Christopher - 1957 - England - Broadcasting, 1957-1967 (Box 183, Folder 1481)
  - Rowland, Christopher - 1957 - England - Broadcasting, 1957-1967 (Box 183, Folder 1482)
  - Rowley, Derrick - 1950 - England - Immunology, 1950-1975 (Box 183, Folder 1483)
  - Roy, Angus - 1932 - England - Physics, 1930-1988 (Box 183, Folder 1484)
  - Ruimschotel, Dick - 1975 - Netherlands - Law, 1974-1986 (Box 183, Folder 1485)
  - Rule, William - 1926 - England - Physics, 1926-1977 (Box 184, Folder 1486)
  - Runcie, John - 1962 - England - American History, 1962-1987 (Box 184, Folder 1487)
  - Runciman, Walter - 1957 - England - Philosophy and Sociology, 1957-1989 (Box 184, Folder 1488)
  - Russell, David - 1937 - England - Philosophy, 1937-1980 (Box 184, Folder 1489)
  - Russell, Joe - 1952 - Scotland - Philosophy, 1951-1985 (Box 184, Folder 1490)
  - Russell, Keith Robert - 1978 - New Zealand - Business, 1978-1987 (Box 184, Folder 1491)
  - Rutherford, Andrew - 1968 - England - Criminology, 1967-1990 (Box 184, Folder 1492)
  - Rutter, Jill Kathleen - 1988 - England - Business Administration, 1987-1992 (Box 184, Folder 1493)
  - Ryan, Harold - 1951 - England - American Building Regulations, 1951-1980 (Box 184, Folder 1494)
  - Ryder, Michael - 1977 - England - History, 1977-1986 (Box 184, Folder 1495)
  - Ryle, Andrew Peter - 1955 - England - Biochemistry, 1955-1989 (Box 184, Folder 1496)
  - Sachrajda, Christopher - 1974 - England - Physics, 1973-1988 (Box 185, Folder 1497)
  - Sallandre, Alain - 1963 - France - Economics and Government, 1963-1968 (Box 185, Folder 1498)
  - Salmon, Roger - 1969 - England - Business Administration, 1968-1988 (Box 185, Folder 1499)
  - Samuel, Edwin - 1931 - England - Economics, 1930-1980 (Box 185, Folder 1500)
  - Sandercock, Edward - 1969 - Australia - Science Education, 1969-1983 (Box 185, Folder 1501)
  - Sandercock, Edward - 1969 - Australia - Science Education, 1969-1983 (Box 185, Folder 1502)
  - Sanders, Neil - 1968 - England - Chemistry, 1967-1988 (Box 185, Folder 1503)
  - Sanderson, Granville - 1968 - England - Sculpture, 1967-1984 (Box 186, Folder 1504)
  - Santelli, Serge - 1968 - France - Architecture, 1967-1973 (Box 186, Folder 1505)
  - Sargent, Kenneth - 1957 - England - Natural Resource Planning, 1957-1988 (Box 186, Folder 1506)
  - Sartain, Wilfred - 1930 - England - Classics, 1930-1974 (Box 186, Folder 1507)
  - Sauerwein, Jacques - 1954 - France - Social Psychology, 1953-1964 (Box 186, Folder 1508)
  - Sauzier, Bertrand - 1973 - England - Cinema Studies, 1974-1978 (Box 186, Folder 1509)
  - Savornin Lohman, Junte - 1974 - Netherlands - Urban Planning, 1974-1986 (Box 187, Folder 1510)
  - Savornin Lohman, Junte - 1974 - Netherlands - Urban Planning, 1974-1986 (Box 187, Folder 1511)
  - Scanlon, Maurice - 1979 - England - Medicine, 1978-1988 (Box 187, Folder 1512)
  - Scheepmaker, Bob - 1960 - Amsterdam - Computer Research, 1959-1975 (Box 187, Folder 1513)
  - Schepers, Gerrit - 1949 - England - Industrial Medicine, 1949-1983 (Box 187, Folder 1514)
  - Scherer, Franz - 1967 - Germany - Economics, 1966-1984 (Box 187, Folder 1515)
  - Schlupp, Friedrich - 1971 - Germany - International Relations, 1970-1975 (Box 187, Folder 1516)
  - Schmidt, Reinhard - 1975 - Germany - Theory of Finance, 1974-1984 (Box 188, Folder 1517)
  - Schmoode, Helge Jan - 1964 - Germany - Economics, 1963-1970 (Box 188, Folder 1518)
  - Scholefield, Bernard - 1925 - England - Surgery, 1925-1981 (Box 188, Folder 1519)
  - Schuhler, Conrad - 1968 - Germany - International Relations, 1967-1970 (Box 188, Folder 1520)
  - Schulz, Dietrich - 1956 - Germany - American Social History, 1956-1977 (Box 188, Folder 1521)
  - Schwarz, Ingo - 1974 - Germany - Computer Science, 1973-1978 (Box 188, Folder 1522)
  - Sciarra, Silvana - 1974 - Italy - Labor Law, 1974-1977 (Box 188, Folder 1523)
  - Sclare, Astor - 1950 - Scotland - Psychiatry, 1950-1980 (Box 189, Folder 1524)
  - Sclater, John - 1962 - England - History and Business Administration, 1962-1988 (Box 189, Folder 1525)
  - Scott, Bowman - 1947 - England - Business Administration, 1947-1984 (Box 189, Folder 1526)
  - Scott, George Peter - 1973 - England - Educational Policy, 1972-1989 (Box 189, Folder 1527)
  - Scott, John Eric - 1958 - England - Medicine, 1957-1987 (Box 189, Folder 1528)
  - Scott, Malcolm - 1961 - England - Nuclear Physics, 1960-1983 (Box 189, Folder 1529)
  - Scrymgour, Peter - 1959 - Australia - Architecture, 1959-1980 (Box 189, Folder 1530)
  - Sculthorpe, Peter - 1985 - Australia - Music, 1964-1985 (Box 190, Folder 1531)
  - Seddon, John - 1955 - England - Aeronautical Engineering, 1955-1976 (Box 190, Folder 1532)
  - Seed, Geoffrey - 1940 - England - History, 1940-1985 (Box 190, Folder 1533)
  - Segers, Marianus - 1974 - Netherlands - Psychology and Comparative Literature, 1973-1986 (Box 190, Folder 1534)
  - Sells, Peter - 1980 - England - Linguistics, 1970-1985 (Box 190, Folder 1535)
  - Setchell, Derrick - 1974 - England - Restorative Dentistry, 1973-1987 (Box 190, Folder 1536)
  - Severin, Giles - 1964 - England - Historical Geography, 1963-1987 (Box 190, Folder 1537)
  - Sfligiotti, Guiseppe - 1961 - Italy - Economics and Business Administration, 1960-1980 (Box 191, Folder 1538)
  - Shakeshaft, John - 1975 - England - History, 1974-1987 (Box 191, Folder 1539)
  - Shapcott, Joanne - 1978 - England - American Literature, 1977-1981 (Box 191, Folder 1540)
  - Shapira, Nathan - 1954 - Israel - Architecture, 1954-1984 (Box 191, Folder 1541)
  - Shapira, Nathan - 1954 - Israel - Architecture, 1954-1984 (Box 191, Folder 1542)
  - Shapira, Nathan - 1954 - Israel - Architecture, 1954-1984 (Box 191, Folder 1543)
  - Sharot, Stephen Andrew - 1968 - England - Sociology, 1967-1980 (Box 191, Folder 1544)
  - Shaw, Duncan - 1956 - England - Chemistry, 1956-1989 (Box 192, Folder 1545)
  - Shaw, Geoffrey Mcintosh - 1953 - Scotland - Theology, 1952-1980 (Box 192, Folder 1546)
  - Shawcross, William - 1972 - England - Political Science and International Relations, 1971-1989 (Box 192, Folder 1547)
  - Shea, Steven Andrew - 1989 - England - Physiology, 1988-1991 (Box 192, Folder 1548)
  - Shears, Laurence William - 1959 - Australia - Education, 1959-1975 (Box 192, Folder 1549)
  - Shears, Michael - 1966 - England - Structural Engineering, 1965-1987 (Box 192, Folder 1550)
  - Shelbourne, Philip - 1949 - England - Law, 1949-1989 (Box 192, Folder 1551)
  - Shennan, Andrew - 1981 - England - International Relations, 1980-1987 (Box 192, Folder 1552)
  - Shephard, Geoffrey Colin - 1953 - England - Mathematics, 1953-1976 (Box 192, Folder 1553)
  - Shepheard, David - 1981 - England - Literature, 1980-1989 (Box 192, Folder 1554)
  - Shepherd, Kenneth John - 1966 - Australia - Civil Engienering, 1965-1967 (Box 193, Folder 1555)
  - Sherwood, Peter Louis Michael - 1963 - England - Business Administration, 1963-1990 (Box 193, Folder 1556)
  - Shone, Obert - 1932 - England - Economics, 1932-1988 (Box 193, Folder 1557)
  - Sibley, Colin Peter - 1988 - England - Physiology, 1987-1990 (Box 193, Folder 1558)
  - Sideri, Sandro - 1965 - Netherlands - Economics, 1964-1976 (Box 193, Folder 1559)
  - Sierksma, Rypke John - 1971 - Netherlands - Social Philosophy, 1971-1985 (Box 193, Folder 1560)
  - Siesby, Erik Oscar - 1954 - Denmark - Law, 1954-1975 (Box 193, Folder 1561)
  - Simeant, Silvere - 1974 - France - Public Administration, 1970-1976 (Box 193, Folder 1562)
  - Simkins, Ethen - 1927 - England - Agricultural Geography, 1927-1988 (Box 194, Folder 1563)
  - Simmers, Ritchie - 1936 - New Zealand - Meteorology, 1936-1984 (Box 194, Folder 1564)
  - Simpson, Alan - 1935 - England - History, 1935-1976 (Box 194, Folder 1565)
  - Simpson, Edward - 1956 - England - Public Administration, 1956-1988 (Box 194, Folder 1566)
  - Simpson, James - 1933 - England - Chemistry, 1933-1952 (Box 194, Folder 1567)
  - Sinclair, Andrew - 1959 - England - Prohibition, 1959-1986 (Box 194, Folder 1568)
  - Sinclair, William Angus - 1930 - England - Philosophy, 1930-1955 (Box 194, Folder 1569)
  - Singer, Malcolm - 1980 - England - Composition, 1979-1990 (Box 195, Folder 1570)
  - Singer, Malcolm - 1980 - England - Composition, 1979-1990 (Box 195, Folder 1571)
  - Singh, Rabinder - 1985 - England - Law, 1984-1989 (Box 195, Folder 1572)
  - Six, Lucas - 1969 - Belgium - Sociology, 1968-1975 (Box 195, Folder 1573)
  - Sixsmith, George - 1977 - England - Russian Poetry, 1976-1986 (Box 195, Folder 1574)
  - Sjoman, Vilgot - 1955 - Sweden - Film, 1954-1975 (Box 195, Folder 1575)
  - Skinner, Andrew - 1929 - England - Education, 1929-1985 (Box 195, Folder 1576)
  - Skinner, Priscilla - 1933 - England - Mathematics, 1933-1960 (Box 196, Folder 1577)
  - Slangen, Herman - 1969 - Netherlands - Philosophy, 1968-1980 (Box 196, Folder 1578)
  - Slessor, Alexander - 1947 - Scotland - Clinical Endocrinology, 1947-1975 (Box 196, Folder 1579)
  - Sloot, Bernardus - 1975 - Netherlands - Sociology, 1974-1979 (Box 196, Folder 1580)
  - Small, Francis - 1963 - New Zealand - International Law, 1963-1986 (Box 196, Folder 1581)
  - Smallwood, Christopher - 1968 - England - Economics, 1967-1985 (Box 196, Folder 1582)
  - Smart, George - 1948 - England - Biomedical Science, 1948-1988 (Box 196, Folder 1583)
  - Smart, James Angus - 1938 - England - American Language, 1938-1983 (Box 197, Folder 1584)
  - Smart, Peter Alastair - 1953 - England - Art History, 1952-1990 (Box 197, Folder 1585)
  - Smith, Amahl - 1988 - England - Philosophy, 1987-1991 (Box 197, Folder 1586)
  - Smith, Charles Richard - 1959 - England - Painting, 1959-1985 (Box 197, Folder 1587)
  - Smith, Colin Smith - 1983 - England - Painting, 1982-1990 (Box 197, Folder 1588)
  - Smith, David Cecil - 1959 - England - Plant Biochemistry, 1958-1988 (Box 197, Folder 1589)
  - Smith, Edward Kinsey - 1965 - England - Medicine, 1964-1975 (Box 197, Folder 1590)
  - Smith, Frederick - 1934 - England - Marine Biology, 1934-1947 (Box 197, Folder 1591)
  - Smith, George - 1949 - England - Cardiology, 1949-1990 (Box 197, Folder 1592)
  - Smith, John Cyril - 1952 - England - Law, 1951-1984 (Box 198, Folder 1593)
  - Smith, Margaret Florence Saumarez - 1931 - England - English Literature, 1931-1979 (Box 198, Folder 1594)
  - Smith, Michael Leonard - 1970 - England - Soviet Studies, 1969-1974 (Box 198, Folder 1595)
  - Smith, Neilson Voyne - 1966 - England - Linguistics, 1965-1983 (Box 198, Folder 1596)
  - Smith, Paul Raymond - 1987 - England - Business Administration, 1986-1991 (Box 198, Folder 1597)
  - Smith, Philip - 1965 - England - Botany, 1964-1985 (Box 198, Folder 1598)
  - Smith, Richard - 1937 - England - Education, 1937-1985 (Box 198, Folder 1599)
  - Smith, Roland - 1983 - England - Classical Studies, 1982-1986 (Box 198, Folder 1600)
  - Smith, Terrence - 1972 - Australia - Art History, 1972-1987 (Box 199, Folder 1601)
  - Smith, Thomas - 1949 - England - Social Statistics, 1950-1983 (Box 199, Folder 1602)
  - Smithies, Arthur - 1932 - England - Economics, 1932-1981 (Box 199, Folder 1603)
  - Smithies, Oliver - 1951 - England - Chemistry, 1950-1964 (Box 199, Folder 1604)
  - Snare, Austin - 1960 - Australia - Mass Communication, 1960-1975 (Box 199, Folder 1605)
  - Snelson, Kenneth - 1955 - England - Water Research Development, 1954-1984 (Box 199, Folder 1606)
  - Sneath, Norman - 1961 - Australia - Structural Engineering, 1961-1981 (Box 199, Folder 1607)
  - Softley, Timothy - 1984 - England - Chemistry, 1983-1990 (Box 199, Folder 1608)
  - Sole, Christopher - 1976 - England - Business Administration, 1975-1986 (Box 199, Folder 1609)
  - Solly, Richard - 1982 - England - American History, 1981-1990 (Box 200, Folder 1610)
  - Solly, Richard - 1982 - England - American History, 1981-1990 (Box 200, Folder 1611)
  - Sommerville, Ian - 1950 - Scotland - Steroid Biochemistry, 1949-1976 (Box 200, Folder 1612)
  - Sonksen, Peter - 1967 - Germany - Diabetes Research, 1966-1988 (Box 200, Folder 1613)
  - Soret, Christine - 1972 - England - Criminal Justice, 1971-1985 (Box 200, Folder 1614)
  - Soskin, David - 1977 - England - Business Administration, 1976-1987 (Box 200, Folder 1615)
  - Soulsby, Hugh - 1928 - England - History, 1928-1987 (Box 200, Folder 1616)
  - Sparrow, Colin - 1980 - England - Mathmatics, 1979-1987 (Box 201, Folder 1617)
  - Sparrow, Malcolm Keith - 1984 - England - Police Studies, 1983-1988 (Box 201, Folder 1618)
  - Sparzani, Antonio - 1971 - Italy - Theoretical Papers, 1970-1975 (Box 201, Folder 1619)
  - Speirs, Ronald - 1953 - England - Theology, 1952-1984 (Box 201, Folder 1620)
  - Spence, Robert - 1928 - England - Chemistry, 1928-1977 (Box 201, Folder 1621)
  - Spencer, Charles Richard - 1932 - England - Education, 1932-1941 (Box 201, Folder 1622)
  - Spillane, John - 1937 - England - Neurology, 1937-1985 (Box 201, Folder 1623)
  - Spitz, Pierre Jean - 1966 - France - International Affairs, 1965-1980 (Box 201, Folder 1624)
  - Spooner, Edward - 1929 - England - Bacteriology, 1929-1983 (Box 202, Folder 1625)
  - Spooner, Frank - 1955 - England - Economic History, 1954-1990 (Box 202, Folder 1626)
  - Springall, Harold - 1936 - England - Chemistry, 1936-1982 (Box 202, Folder 1627)
  - Stalker, Harry - 1947 - Scotland - Medicine, 1947-1986 (Box 202, Folder 1628)
  - Stallworthy, Wendy - 1968 - England - American Literature, 1968-1988 (Box 202, Folder 1629)
  - Standage, Simon - 1967 - England - Violin, 1966-1986 (Box 202, Folder 1630)
  - Stark, George - 1931 - Scotland - Negro Education, 1930-1952 (Box 203, Folder 1631)
  - Steeds, David - 1964 - England - Politics and Economics, 1964-1976 (Box 203, Folder 1632)
  - Steele, Catherine - 1928 - Scotland - Organic Chemistry, 1928-1984 (Box 203, Folder 1633)
  - Steele, John - 1963 - England - Economics, 1963-1988 (Box 203, Folder 1634)
  - Steele, Sydney - 1930 - England - Engineering, 1930-1983 (Box 203, Folder 1635)
  - Steenbergen, Theodore - 1957 - Netherlands - Automation, 1956-1968 (Box 203, Folder 1636)
  - Stephen, Barrie Michael Lace - 1970 - England - Law, 1969-1985 (Box 203, Folder 1637)
  - Stephens, Nicholas - 1963 - England - Sculpture, 1962-1981 (Box 204, Folder 1638)
  - Stephenson, George - 1925 - England - Chemical Engineering, 1925-1980 (Box 204, Folder 1639)
  - Stephenson, Gordon - 1936 - England - Architecture, 1936-1987 (Box 204, Folder 1640)
  - Stephenson, Gordon - 1936 - England - Architecture, 1936-1987 (Box 204, Folder 1641)
  - Stephenson, Gordon - 1936 - England - Architecture, 1936-1987 (Box 204, Folder 1642)
  - Stephenson, Hugh - 1962 - England - History and Economics, 1962-1989 (Box 204, Folder 1643)
  - Stevens, Jack - 1957 - England - Surgery, 1956-1984 (Box 205, Folder 1644)
  - Stewartd, Helen Catherine - 1989 - England - Philosophy, 1988-1989 (Box 205, Folder 1645)
  - Stewart, David - 1969 - England - Business and Industrial Studies, 1969-1984 (Box 205, Folder 1646)
  - Stewart, Ian - 1948 - Scotland - Economics, 1948-1988 (Box 205, Folder 1647)
  - Stewart, Jean - 1932 - England - American Literature, 1932-1988 (Box 205, Folder 1648)
  - Stewart, Ronald - 1973 - England - Astrophysics, 1972-1986 (Box 205, Folder 1649)
  - Stewart. Shaun - 1960 - England - Tariff Protection, 1960-1988 (Box 205, Folder 1650)
  - Stiller, Eric - 1932 - England - Organic Chemistry, 1932-1954 (Box 206, Folder 1651)
  - Stocker, Bruce - 1951 - England - Microbiology, 1951-1970 (Box 206, Folder 1652)
  - Stone, Frank - 1950 - England - Chemistry, 1949-1984 (Box 206, Folder 1653)
  - Stone, Leslie Charles - 1958 - England - Modern American Politics, 1958-1989 (Box 206, Folder 1654)
  - Stopford, Henry Philip - 1977 - England - Law, 1977-1988 (Box 206, Folder 1655)
  - Storey, Kate Gillian - 1987 - England - Zoology, 1986-1989 (Box 206, Folder 1656)
  - Stow, Julian Randolph - 1964 - Australia - Writing, 1964-1985 (Box 206, Folder 1657)
  - Story, Richard - 1933 - England - Astronomy, 1933-1987 (Box 206, Folder 1658)
  - Strack, Fritz - 1974 - Germany - Psychology, 1973-1984 (Box 206, Folder 1659)
  - Strain, Alastair - 1978 - England - Biochemistry, 1977-1990 (Box 207, Folder 1660)
  - Strawbridge, Peter David - 1989 - England - Police Studies, 1988-1992 (Box 207, Folder 1661)
  - Streeck, Wolfgang - 1972 - Germany - Sociology, 1971-1977 (Box 207, Folder 1662)
  - Street, Harry - 1947 - England - Law, 1947-1984 (Box 207, Folder 1663)
  - Strittmatter, Peter - 1964 - England - Astrophysics, 1963-1976 (Box 207, Folder 1664)
  - Strong, Thomas - 1948 - Australia - Agricultural Economics, 1948-1981 (Box 207, Folder 1665)
  - Stubbs, Lionel - 1955 - England - Plant Virology, 1955-1975 (Box 207, Folder 1666)
  - Studdert-Kennedy, William - 1962 - England - Political Science, 1961-1989 (Box 207, Folder 1667)
  - Sturrock, Alexander - 1951 - Scotland - Public Relations, 1950-1967 (Box 208, Folder 1668)
  - Sturrock, John - 1984 - England - Law, 1983-1990 (Box 208, Folder 1669)
  - Stutzer, Walter - 1958 - Switzerland - American Foreign Policy, 1957-1975 (Box 208, Folder 1670)
  - Styler, Geoffrey - 1938 - England - Theology, 1938-1975 (Box 208, Folder 1671)
  - Sugar, Peter Charles - 1958 - Hungary - Industrialized Techniques, 1958-1981 (Box 208, Folder 1672)
  - Sullivan, Andrew - 1984 - England - Political Science, 1983-1990 (Box 208, Folder 1673)
  - Suss, Karl-Heinz - 1977 - Germany - Literature, 1976-1985 (Box 208, Folder 1674)
  - Sutcliffe, Robert - 1962 - England - Economics, 1961-1981 (Box 208, Folder 1675)
  - Sutherland, Gordon - 1931 - England - Physics, 1931-1981 (Box 209, Folder 1676)
  - Sutherland, Hugh - 1931 - England - Political Science, 1931-1980 (Box 209, Folder 1677)
  - Swaab, Peter - 1979 - England - American Literature, 1978-1989 (Box 209, Folder 1678)
  - Sweet, John Philip - 1954 - England - Theology, 1954-1984 (Box 209, Folder 1679)
  - Sweetman, Donald - 1957 - England - Nuclear Physics, 1956-1980 (Box 209, Folder 1680)
  - Swift, Eleanor - 1931 - England - History, 1931-1990 (Box 209, Folder 1681)
  - Swinnerton-Dyer, Henry - 1954 - England - Mathematics, 1954-1990 (Box 209, Folder 1682)
  - Sykes, Richard - 1957 - England - Philosophy, 1956-1976 (Box 209, Folder 1683)
  - Sypkens, Henricus Andre - 1965 - Netherlands - Business Studies, 1964-1985 (Box 209, Folder 1684)
  - Tacey, David John - 1982 - Australia - Literature, 1981-1985 (Box 210, Folder 1685)
  - Tagg, Eric Donavan - 1935 - England - Mathematics, 1935-1968 (Box 210, Folder 1686)
  - Tagliaferri, Aldo - 1957 - Italy - Literature, 1956-1976 (Box 210, Folder 1687)
  - Tait, Malcolm - 1961 - New Zealand - Music, 1961-1980 (Box 210, Folder 1688)
  - Talbot, James - 1976 - England - History, 1976-1984 (Box 210, Folder 1689)
  - Talbot, William - 1931 - England - Geography, 1931-1983 (Box 210, Folder 1690)
  - Tambini, Luigi - 1959 - Italy - Economics, 1959-1981 (Box 210, Folder 1691)
  - Tancibudek, Sandra - 1980 - Australia - Music, 1979-1985 (Box 210, Folder 1692)
  - Tanner, Paul - 1958 - England - American Literature, 1957-1975 (Box 210, Folder 1693)
  - Tanner, Ross Murray - 1981 - New Zealand - Public Policy, 1981-1986 (Box 211, Folder 1694)
  - Tanquery, David Andrew - 1966 - England - Computer Science, 1965-1975 (Box 211, Folder 1695)
  - Tatham, George - 1932 - England - Geography, 1932-1956 (Box 211, Folder 1696)
  - Tattam, Charles - 1930 - Australia - Geophysics, 1930-1987 (Box 211, Folder 1697)
  - Tayler, Roger - 1953 - England - Astronomy, 1953-1990 (Box 211, Folder 1698)
  - Taylor, Charles Kenneth - 1965 - Australia - Political History, 1964-1985 (Box 211, Folder 1699)
  - Taylor, Christopher - 1963 - England - Business Administration, 1963-1987 (Box 211, Folder 1700)
  - Taylor, Edward - 1936 - England - Physical Chemistry, 1936-1979 (Box 211, Folder 1701)
  - Taylor, George - 1928 - England - History, 1928-1990 (Box 212, Folder 1702)
  - Taylor, John Bryan - 1959 - England - Physics, 1959-1985 (Box 212, Folder 1703)
  - Taylor, John Gerald - 1956 - England - Physics, 1956-1974 (Box 212, Folder 1704)
  - Taylor, John Robert - 1960 - England - Physics, 1959-1975 (Box 212, Folder 1705)
  - Taylor, Len - 1949 - England - Psychology, 1949-1979 (Box 212, Folder 1706)
  - Taylor, Mark - 1976 - England - Art Education, 1976-1987 (Box 212, Folder 1707)
  - Taylor, Stephan - 1981 - England - Business Administration, 1981-1984 (Box 212, Folder 1708)
  - Tebay, Michel Dion - 1971 - England - Business Administration, 1970-1989 (Box 212, Folder 1709)
  - Tempest, Norton - 1930 - England - Education, 1930-1987 (Box 213, Folder 1710)
  - Ter Meulen, Alice - 1976 - Netherlands - Philosophy, 1975-1980 (Box 213, Folder 1711)
  - Tervet, Ian - 1933 - Scotland - Botany, 1935-1954 (Box 213, Folder 1712)
  - Terzani, Tiziano - 1967 - Italy - International Relations, 1967-1987 (Box 213, Folder 1713)
  - Thackery, A. David - 1934 - England - Astrophysics, 1935-1978 (Box 213, Folder 1714)
  - Thistlethwaite, Frank - 1938 - England - American History, 1937-1989 (Box 213, Folder 1715)
  - Thompson, Bertha - 1931 - England - Icelandic Studies, 1931-1981 (Box 213, Folder 1716)
  - Thompson, Edith Bruce - 1928 - England - History, 1927-1956 (Box 213, Folder 1717)
  - Thompson, John - 1963 - England - American History, 1963-1979 (Box 213, Folder 1718)
  - Thompson, Michael - 1973 - England - Physiology, 1972-1988 (Box 214, Folder 1719)
  - Thompson, Peter - 1976 - England - Physiology, 1976-1980 (Box 214, Folder 1720)
  - Thompson, Ronald Bolton - 1952 - England - Hematology, 1951-1975 (Box 214, Folder 1721)
  - Thomson, James - 1950 - England - Logic, 1950-1956 (Box 214, Folder 1722)
  - Thorne, Anthony - 1954 - England - Public Health, 1954-1979 (Box 214, Folder 1723)
  - Thornley, John - 1962 - England - Physics, 1961-1990 (Box 214, Folder 1724)
  - Thurn, Georg - 1976 - Germany - Political Science, 1974-1986 (Box 214, Folder 1725)
  - Thygesen, Niels - 1960 - Denmark - Economics, 1959-1976 (Box 214, Folder 1726)
  - Timmermans, Alphons - 1972 - Netherlands - System Science, 1971-1979 (Box 215, Folder 1727)
  - Tiver, Newton Stanley - 1960 - Australia - Agriculture, 1960-1985 (Box 215, Folder 1728)
  - Tiver, Newton Stanley - 1960 - Australia - Agriculture, 1960-1985 (Box 215, Folder 1729)
  - Toinet, Marie France - 1968 - France - Political Science, 1967-1980 (Box 215, Folder 1730)
  - Tomlinson, Richard Peter - 1983 - England - History, 1982-1987 (Box 215, Folder 1731)
  - Toomer, Gerald - 1959 - England - Math, 1959-1975 (Box 215, Folder 1732)
  - Torri, Michelguglielmo - 1973 - Italy - History, 1970-1983 (Box 215, Folder 1733)
  - Trapnell, Barry - 1950 - England - Chemistry, 1949-1984 (Box 215, Folder 1734)
  - Trautz, Fritz - 1953 - Germany - History, 1953-1975 (Box 216, Folder 1735)
  - Trendle, Neville - 1975 - New Zealand - Law, 1974-1987 (Box 216, Folder 1736)
  - Treu, Tiziano - 1962 - Italy - Law, 1962-1975 (Box 216, Folder 1737)
  - Trevor, Jack - 1934 - England - Anthropology, 1934-1967 (Box 216, Folder 1738)
  - Trickett, Mabel Rachel - 1949 - England - English Literature, 1949-1990 (Box 216, Folder 1739)
  - Trist, Eric - 1933 - England - Psychology, 1933-1985 (Box 216, Folder 1740)
  - Triulzi, Alessandro - 1968 - Italy - History, 1968-1975 (Box 216, Folder 1741)
  - Truscott, David - 1932 - England - Engineering, 1932-1989 (Box 217, Folder 1742)
  - Tucker, Rodney - 1975 - Australia - Electronics, 1974-1985 (Box 217, Folder 1743)